fbisocial.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Statement

This website is operated and administered by Community Engine Pty Ltd (“Community Engine”, “we”, “us”, “our”). We care about your privacy. This policy sets out in detail how we manage the personal information you provide to us.

We respect your rights to privacy under the Privacy Act 1998. We will not use or disclose your personal information other than for the purposes of collection described in this policy or for purposes for which we have received your consent.

**When and how do we collect personal information?**

“Personal information” is any information that can be used to identify you. We will only collect personal information about you if you provide it to us knowingly. We will provide you with access to the information we hold about you if you so request. You may also advise us of any errors or matters that need updating relating to your personal information and we will amend your personal information accordingly. Please direct such requests in writing to the following address: privacy@communityengine.com

**What information do we collect?**

When you register as a member of this website, or contact us, we collect your full name, email address, telephone number, address, and other details from time to time as listed on the registration form. We use this information to provide our services to you and to administer the website, as well as for the other purposes set out in this policy.

We also sometimes use “cookies” and “log files” to store your preferences, record session information and collect information on how you visit and access our web pages. This information is collected automatically whenever you use this website. Cookies and log files do not include personal information that is able to identify you.

**What about personal information I post on the website or give to other users?**

We do not take any responsibility for any personal information or other details that you post on the website or give to other users of the website. Although we recommend that you do not post or share personal information or other details on the website that you do not want made publicly available, you are solely responsible for the personal information and other details that you post or share on the website.

**What do we do with the information?**

We will only use or disclose your personal information for the purposes for which you have provided it to us, unless:

you have consented to the use or disclosure; or

it is necessary to comply with the law.

We use your personal information to deliver our services to you and to keep you up to date with events that may be of interest to you. Our related entities and business affiliates may also contact you about our other services or products that may be of interest to you.

As a necessary adjunct to the proper operation and administration of this website, we need to provide your personal information to Community Engine staff and technical contractors. Such staff and technical contractors are subject to obligations of confidentiality to us, and you authorise them to gain access to personal information as part of their services to us.

Your personal information is collected so that we and our related entities and business affiliates can promote and market our/their services to you (including by way of direct mail, telemarketing, email, SMS and MMS messages). This is to keep you informed of products, services and special offers and may continue after you cease acquiring services from us. If you do not wish Community Engine or its related bodies and business affiliates to promote and market products, services and special offers to you, please contact:privacy@communityengine.com

**How do we use “cookies” and “log files”?**

As part of offering and providing customisable and personalised services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your Internet web browser from our web server and stored on your computer. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your computer does not accept them.

We may also log IP addresses (i.e. the electronic addresses of computers connected to the Internet) to analyse trends, administer the website, track users movements on the website, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use and for advertisers and business partners.

What do we do to safeguard personal information?

We take reasonable steps to preserve the security of your personal information and other information or data processed through the website. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as perfectly secure. As a result, although we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you transmit such information at your own risk.

Once we have received data information you transmit to us, we implement reasonable measures to protect the security of the information in our own systems including restricting physical access to your personal information and using firewalls and secure databases.

**What about links to other websites?**

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. This website may contain links to other sites. We make no representations or warranties as to the privacy practices of any site operated by a third party and are not responsible for the privacy policies of such sites.

We recommend that you examine the privacy policy for all third party websites you visit to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

**What if our privacy policy changes?**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting an updated version of the policy on this website. You should visit this page periodically to review the privacy policy for changes.

**What should I do if I have any privacy-related complaints or enquiries?**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or any complaint regarding treatment of your privacy by us, please email: [privacy@communityengine.com](mailto:privacy@communityengine.com)
